My role would be serving the customers every day
Always putting the customers first is what they say
I've worked for this firm almost my whole career now
But I am finding that it is getting boring somehow
So I am gonna break away and stand!
Gotta give it a try and take command!
What that means is I am taking the wheel!
Making my dream into something so real!
She is really demanding so it is been stressful lately
I need some time just lying on a beach greatly
Doing absolutely nothing and just forgetting it all
But instead I will answer this loud inner call
So I am gonna break away and stand!
Gotta give it a try and take command!
What that means is I am taking the wheel!
Making my dream into something so real!
I was planning to give my official notice tomorrow
Leaving behind all this hesitation and this sorrow
I accept a new position that I have created myself
Putting my own hard-earned dreams up on the shelf
So I am gonna break away and stand!
Gotta give it a try and take command!
What that means is I am taking the wheel!
Making my dream into something so real!
Yes I am gonna break away and stand!
Gotta give it a try and take command!
What that means is I am taking the wheel!
Making my dream into something so real!
I'm searching for something, I found it today
I am walking on this brand-new highway